Scooby-Doo! Shaggy's Showdown is a animation, family,
mystery film directed by Matt Peters.
When the Scooby gang visits a dude ranch, they discover that it and the nearby town have been
haunted by a ghostly cowboy, Dapper Jack, who fires real fire from his fire irons.
The mystery only deepens when it’s discovered that the ghost is
also the long lost relative of Shaggy Rogers!
Scooby-Doo / Fred (voice), played by Frank Welker.
Daphne (voice), played by Grey DeLisle.
Shaggy (voice), played by Matthew Lillard.
Velma (voice), played by Kate Micucci.
Larry (voice), played by Carlos Alazraqui.
Buddy G. (voice), played by Max Charles.
Scooby-Doo!
Shaggy's Showdown is a 2017 direct-to-DVD animated western comedy mystery film, and the
twenty-eighth entry in the direct-to-video series of Scooby-Doo films.
It was released digitally on January 31, 2017, and on DVD on February 14, 2017.
The film explores themes of friendship, ranch, talking dog, cowboy, ghost.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking and mind_bending.